<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<contrato_SPA>
    <commoditie>
        <sugar>ICUMSA 45</sugar>
        <color>White</color></commoditie>
<heat_01 FCO="FCO-A20230101-IC45-400KMT-IBER-XXXXX-P0RT"></heat_01>
    <issue Date="Tuesday, December 20, 2022"></issue>
    <expiration Date="Friday, December 23, 2022"></expiration>
    <to mr=""></to>
    <att mr=""></att>
    <via mr="Mr. xxxxxxxxxx / XXX" mrs="XXXXXXXXXX / Via: Mr. Antonio – CMO, IBER OUTDOORS S.L"></via>
    <via mr="Mr. Antonio CMO, IBER OUTDOORS S.L"></via>
<EMPTY/>
<customer_A>IBER OUTDOORS S.L.</customer_A>
    <issue Date="Tuesday, December 20, 2022"></issue>
    <expiration Date="Friday, December 23, 2022"></expiration>
    <to mr=""></to>
    <att mr=""></att>
    <via mr="Mr. xxxxxxxxxx / XXX" mrs="XXXXXXXXXX / via: Mr. Antonio – CMO, IBER OUTDOORS S.L"></via>
    <via mr="Mr. Antonio – CMO, IBER OUTDOORS S.L"></via>
<EMPTY/>
<customer_B>XXXXXXXXXXXXXX</customer_B>
    <the Exporter="Tuesday, December 20, 2022"></the>
    <company Name="IBER OUTDOORS S.L."></company>
    <to mr=""></to>
    <att mr=""></att>
    <via mr="Mr. xxxxxxxxxx / XXX" mrs="XXXXXXXXXX / Via: Mr. Antonio – CMO, IBER OUTDOORS S.L">
        </via>
<![CDATA[FULL CORPORATE OFFER nº: FCO-A20221220-IC45-60MMT-IBER-SURAN\n
BETWEEN:\n

THE EXPORTER / FCO-A20221220-IC45-60MMT-IBER-SURAN\n
Company Name:	IBER OUTDOORS S.L.
Address Registration:	Pza, María Conesa nº: 1, ZIP: 12500, Vinaròs / Castellón–Spain.\n
Registry Number:	CIF nº: B-12975538 / VIES nº: ESB12975538\n
Representative / Title:	Mr. Ángel González Rodríguez / CFO.\n
Passport / Nationality:	PAN096338 / Spanish.
Telephone and Address @:	(+34 644 888 092) / cfo@iberoutdoors.com 
Name of the Bank:	CAIXABANK
Bank Address:	C/ Dr. Ricardo Santos nº:10, C.P: 12500, Vinarós, Castellón-Spain.
Account Name:	IBER OUTDOORS S.L.
Swift Code:	CAIXESBBXXX

AND

THE BUYER / FCO-A20221220-IC45-60MMT-IBER-SURAN
Company Name:	SURANEXPORT SAS LLC.
Address Registration:	
Registry Number:	
Representative / Title:	
Passport / Nationality:	
Phone and Address @:	
Name of The Issuing Bank:	
Bank Address:	
Swift Code:	
Name confirmate Bank:	
Swift Code:

We, the Company IBER OUTDOORS S.L, or Exporter, with registration number: CIF nº: B-12975538 / VIES nº: ESB12975538, and registered office located at, Pza, María Conesa, nº: 1, ZIP: 12500, Vinaròs / Castellón-Spain, represented by, Mr. Ángel González / CFO, with sufficient Corporate and legal authority to sign this Full Corporate Offer nº:                       FCO-A20221220-IC45-60MMT-IBER-SURAN.

We communicate that;

After having received, from the Company, CONSORCIO 4WEBMED AGROINDUSTRIAL INC, proposal LOI nº: Miami_December_14th_2022, as Buyer's verbal agent, issues the following, Full Corporate Offer nº: FCO-A20221220-IC45-60MMT-IBER-SURAN, of the product, (UREA 46%), for a period of 1 Year, in 250.000M MT Month x 12 Months, to establish from the moment of its signature and acceptance by the Importer, the conditions, prices, volumes, etc..., under the terms agreed below.

1.	PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS:
     The final specifications will be delivered to ICPO or SPA.

2.	GENERAL PRODUCT TERMS AND CONDITIONS
•	Port of Origin: xxxxxxxxxxxxxx / Others.
•	Port of Destination: Base CIF, Port of xxxxxxxxx / xxxxxxxxxx.
•	50.000 MT (Metric Ton) (+/-5%) Month x 12, 
•	Total Quantity Contracted: 60.000.000 MT (Metric Tons) (+/-5%) in 3.000.00TM x 12 Months (Costs, Freight and Insurance).
•	Packing: Bag 50Kg.
•	Inspection: At the loading port by SGS or Similar, report for quality and quantity.
•	Shipping terms: INCOTERMS 2010/20, Base CIF, Port of Colombia / Ecuador / Perú (Costs, Freight and Insurance).
•	Shipping schedule: SPA.

3.	PRICE
•	Price per 1 MT (Metric Tons) (+/- 5%), INCOTERMS 2010/2020 Base CIF, Port of xxxxxxxxxxxxx / xxxxxxx (Costs, Freight and Insurance): USD $310 (Three Hundred Ten US Dollars).
•	Total Quantity Contracted: 60.000.000 MT (Metric Tons) (+/-5%).
•	Total Contract Amount: 60.000.000 MT x USD $310 = USD $930.000.000M (Nine Hundred Thirty Million US Dollars).
•	Quantity First Shipment: 3.000.000 MT (Metric Tons) (+/-5%).
•	Amount First Shipment: 3.000.000 MT x USD $310 = USD $77.500.000M (Seventy-Seven Million with Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars). 
•	Amount per Shipment of xxx.000 MT: xxx.000 MT x USD $xxx = USD $xxxxxxxx  (xxxxxx Million with xxxxxxxxxx Hundred Thousand US Dollars).  
•	Remaining Months, INCOTERMS 2010/2020 Base CIF, Port of xxxxxxxxx / xxxxxx (Costs, Freight and Insurance): 57.000.000 MT x 11 Months.
•	The indicative price per 1 MT (1 Metric Ton), INCOTERMS 2010/2020 Base CIF, Port of xxxxxxxxxxxxx / xxxxxxxx (Costs, Freight and Insurance) of the product, will be provided by the Exporter to the Importer in the SPA Contract.


4.	METHOD OF PAYMENT
•  Payment of the amount corresponding to the amount of the monthly supply of the product, via SWIFT MT-103 to the Exporter's bank account, against documents that are reflected in the SPA.
•	To do this, prior to the start of the product supply and shipment process, the Buyer must issue a Standby Letter of Credit (SBLC) in favor of the Exporter, valid for 366 days for the amount of USD $xxxxxxx.000M (xxxxxxxxxxx Million with xxxxx Hundred Thousand US Dollars) of the product shipment as guarantee, 100% Irrevocable, Transferable, Assignable, Negotiable, Operative, Confirmed, UCP600, conditioned against SPA documents.
•	In the three banking days following the delivery of all the obligation documents that will reflect the SPA, the Buyer's Bank will pay the amount corresponding to the amount of the monthly supply of the product, via SWIFT MT-103/TT, to the bank account of the Exporter.
•	The Payment Instrument must be issued by a TOP 25-50 international bank.
•	The Exporter issues a 2% Performance Guarantee in favor of the Buyer after the verification/confirmation of the bank instrument (SBLC) by the Exporter's bank.

5.	PROCESS
1.	The Importer/Buyer issues a Letter of Intent (LOI).

2.	The Exporter issues a Full Corporate Offer (FCO).

3.	The Importer signs, seals and returns the FCO to the Exporter with the ICPO open to changes and Simple Proof of Funds (POF) in the name of the Exporter, where it indicates the capacity and availability for the issuance of a Standby Letter of Credit (SBLC) in favor of the Exporter, valid for 366 days in guarantee, for the amount of USD $xxxxxxx.000M (xxxxxxxxxx Million xxxxxxx Hundred Thousand American Dollars), to acquire the product xxxxxxxxxxxxxx.

4.	The Exporter, upon receiving the FCO, ICPO and simple POF, the Exporter issues a Pro-forma Invoice, a Draft Contract (SPA) that will incorporate the complete terms and conditions and requests the certificate of existence and capacity of the manufacturer.

5.	Both PARTIES, with the regularization, acceptance and confirmation of the SPA contract, sign it, seal it, return it, together with the corresponding ICPO and with the legalization of the ICPO and SPA in their respective banks, the Exporter, sends to the Email of the Importer's bank with a copy for the Importer of the manufacturer's certificate indicating that it is ready, willing and able to supply the xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx product.

6.	Once these communications have been made, clarified and all the issues referred to between the Banks have been made by corporate bank mail, sends a Draft of the verbiage of the SBLC as guarantee to the buyer's bank officer (to avoid errors and unnecessary expenses). 

7.	Once the pertinent adjustments have been made in the SBLC, the Buyer orders his bank to issue the SBLC in favor of the Exporter for payment of the shipment and sends it to the Exporter's bank through the SWIFT system.
The shipment will begin within 10 business days following the confirmation of SBLC by the Exporter's bank.

8.	The Buyer's bank makes the payment to the Exporter's bank immediately (SWIFT MT-103/TT) after loading the material, against the obligation documents of the SPA Port of origin, SGS, 110% Secure.
6.	NON-RIDING AND NON-DISCLOSURE, CONFIDENTIALITY AND PENALTY

THE PARTIES ACCEPT AND AGREE to the provisions of the international chamber of commerce, Geneva, Switzerland for non-circumvention and non-disclosure with respect to each and every party involved in this transaction and contract, additions, renewals and transfers of third parties, with full reciprocity for a period of (5) five years from the date of issuance of this document.

Both PARTIES will keep as confidential any information received between them, and that is identified as such, whether it has been revealed verbally or in writing, and will only use it for the purposes contemplated in the CLAC, SCO, FCO, ICPO or Contract.

Confidential information will not be considered that which is or will become public knowledge, without THE PARTIES being responsible for its disclosure.
In the case of unjustified DISCLOSURE, a claim for disclosure will be processed in the courts and country designated by the injured party.

7.	FINAL TERMS
•	The Buyer's Bank, once the RWA has been sent and responded with the POP, will carry out the Due Diligence (DD) of the Proof of Product (POP), and if everything is Correct, the Buyer's Bank will irrevocably send the SBLC to the Exporter's Bank.
•	All bank expenses that imply the management and settlement of the financial instrument of payment in the Exporter's bank account will be borne by the Buyer, who will be responsible for the payment by crediting the account of the former, of the budget issued by the Exporter's Bank or negotiation in payment agreement between banks.

          ASSIGNMENT / SUBROGATION:

•	This FCO is subrogable and transferable by any of the PARTIES, prior written notice to the other party.
•	The subrogation or transfer of the FCO must maintain the terms and conditions of the same FCO unless the PARTIES MUTUALLY AGREE AND ACCEPT THE CHANGES.
•	The FCO, which is subrogated or transferred, will be fully binding for the final ICPO and SPA of the operation and frees the subrogant from any legal or Juridical PROBLEM that may arise between the subrogated PARTIES, once the subrogation is subrogated and said subrogation is accepted between the parts.]]>
</contrato_SPA>
